A Guide to the Daniel E. Wright Papers, 1903-1973
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- WWII; Newspaper Clippings 1941-43 (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Military Parade
  - "Interpreting War News"
  - "Career Men Conduct Underhand"
  - "Purge of Pro-Welles Diplomats"
  - "Pearson Calls Steinhardt, U.S. Envoy to Turkey"
  - "Lehman is Elected Head of UN Relief"
  - "The Flying Tigers"
  - "Interpreting War News"
  - "U.N. Conference at White House"
  - "U.N. Group Intends Aiding Those Now Stricken"
  - "49 Nations to Help Victims of War"
  - "U.S. Rationing"
  - "New League of Nations!"
  - "The Guards and the Ghost"
- WWII, Printed Materials 1941-44 (Box-folder 2:6)
  - Greek Interpreter Dialogue & Dictionary
  - "The Truth About Pearl Harbor" by John T. Flynn 1944
  - "Handbook for Military Intelligence Interpreters: French"
  - "Handbook on Foreign Maps"
  - "Health, Medicine, and Sanitation in Bulgaria" by Alexandra Feldmahn 1943
  - Postcards
  - "So You Had a Virus?"
  - "The United States in a New World: Relations with Britain"
  - "The U.S. in a New World; The Domestic Economy"
- WWII, Speeches and Reports 1941-43 (Box-folder 2:7)
  - "Our Illusions of Freedom" by Colby Dorr Dam
  - "The Human Spirit can Win Peace" by Colby Dorr Dam
- Wright, Grace Y. 1951-73 (Box-folder 2:8)
  - Mrs. Hunt 1951
  - Frank Shirk 1961, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969
  - R. M. Larimer 1970
  - "The Facts about Your Income Tax"
  - "Vietnam Events Parallel China of 20 Years Ago"
  - "Have a Good Cry and Live Longer"
  - Miscellaneous cancelled stamps and envelopes
  - "Observations on Greece in 1972" by M.C. Balfor
- Commissions and Memorabilia (Box 3)
  - Army Camp Kit
  - Ceramic Greek Donkey
  - Commission for Senior Sanitary Engineer, 1941
  - Commission for Sanitary Engineer Director 1944
  - Three Wooden Camels
  - WWII German Mug
  - WWII German Plate
  - Handle from a Vessel, Marked "from Tyre"